<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog RSS</title><link>http://www.wekaplan.us/weka-blog/</link><pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2017 00:20:04 +0000</pubDate><item><title><![CDATA[SBA Announces National Small Business Week]]></title><link>http://www.wekaplan.us/weka-blog/6-top-tips-for-a-tip-top-blog/</link><description><![CDATA[WASHINGTON – On May 1 st, the head of the U.S. Small Business Administration (SBA), Administrator Maria Contreras-Sweet announced that this year’s National Small Business Week will be held from May 1-7.  This year’s theme will be “Dream Big, Start Small.”
Contreras-Sweet will start the week in Washington, D.C., where she will recognize and award outstanding small business owners from around the country. She will then continue the week with small business events in Atlanta, Denver, Phoenix, and]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 02 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What SBA Loan Is For You.]]></title><link>http://www.wekaplan.us/weka-blog/to-blog-or-not-to-blog-blog.-of-course-wed-say-that/</link><description><![CDATA[If you’re planning to start a business or expand an existing business, you might need financing help. SBA participates in a number of loan programs designed for business owners who may have trouble qualifying for a traditional bank loan.
To start the process, you should visit a local bank or lending institution that participates in SBA programs. SBA loan applications are structured to meet SBA requirements, so that the loan is eligible for an SBA guarantee. This guarantee represents the portion]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[What SBA Offers to Help Small Businesses Grow]]></title><link>http://www.wekaplan.us/weka-blog/welcome-to-our-blog-but-what-is-it/</link><description><![CDATA[What does SBA offer to small business owners? The programs are many and varied, and the qualifications for each are specific. SBA can help facilitate a loan for you with a third party lender, guarantee a bond, or help you find venture capital. Understanding how SBA works is the first step towards receiving assistance.
SBA’s Role
SBA provides a number of financial assistance programs for small businesses that have been specifically designed to meet key financing needs, including debt financing,]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 29 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Is Your Small Business Ready to Sell to the Government?]]></title><link>http://www.wekaplan.us/weka-blog/why-your-titles-should-be-no-longer-than-this/</link><description><![CDATA[When you're writing your next post, consider this: 80% of people will read your blog headline, but only 20% will stay for the rest.  
So, if headlines are 400% more important than what comes after them (where there’s already ever-increasing competition to attract eyes), you need to be more concise than ever to get attention.

The Importance of Title Length
A guide on the right length for your post titles

If you want to keep your followers’ attention while conveying your brilliant wordplay, keep]]></description><pubDate>Fri, 05 Dec 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate></item></channel></rss>
